Contact

katy.probasco@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/katy-probasco1408 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership
Training
PowerPoint

Katy Probasco AANP, FNP-BC

Family Nurse Practitioner

Dallas, Texas

Summary

Family Nurse Practitioner with a passion for caring for other deserving humans! Strong sense of responsibility to know the best healthcare practices, establishing strong patient-provider relationships, and helping persons maintain health, and manage life. Experienced and excited to provide education to patients, and new health providers.

Experience

Baylor University Medical Center Registered Nurse March 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Baylor Scott & White Health RN March 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months) Dallas, Texas

Medical Solutions
Travel Registered Nurse
January 2016 - Present (4 years 6 months)
Anywhere!

United Surgical Partners International, Inc Clinical Nurse Manager 2016 - 2016 (less than a year) Fountain Valley, California

Fountain Valley Regional Medical Center Registered Nurse November 2014 - June 2015 (8 months)

Responsibilities included patient education, sedation and phase to recovery care in an out-patient endoscopy setting. Also, daily duties included equipment

setup and sterilization, assisting the physician, specimen collection, electronic charting, intravenous medication administration.

Personally researched SGNA standards and updated policies and procedures.

Hoag Hospital Registered Nurse 2015 - 2015 (less than a year) Newport Beach, California

Responsibilities include patient care in an endoscopy suite working alongside physicians to provide the best care.

University Medical Center Registered Nurse July 2009 - June 2014 (5 years) Lubbock, Texas

Covenant Medical Center Registered Nurse May 2008 - July 2009 (1 year 3 months) Lubbock, Texas

Education

Simmons College

Master of Science (MS), Family Practice Nurse/Nursing (2017 - 2019)

Lubbock Christian University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2012 - 2015)

Covenant School of Nursing and Allied Health
Diploma in Registered Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2006 - 2008)